

# MARCUS BODIN

Driven and creative 26-year-old with a keen interest in leadership and product and service development.

Driven by new challenges and project based problem solving.

An overall team player with a passion for all kinds of technology.



0707507897

marcus.v.bodin@gmail.com Vasavägen 23b 582 20, Linköping

se.linkedin.com/in/bodinmarcus

### Work Experience

#### Product Development Engineer

Combitech, Linköping Jun 2016 -

#### Package Designer

Skandinaviska Försäljningsgruppen, Linköping May 2015 - Sep 2015

#### Design Engineer Intern

Scania CV, Södetälje Jun 2015 - Aug 2015

#### Summer and part time jobs

Linköping University and ICA Supermarket, Stockholm Aug 2010 - Dec 2015

Enrolled in the Combitech Talent Program. Currently assigned as a consultant at SAAB Aeronotics. Work tasks involve design of parts for mechanical installation in SAAB Gripen E.

Consultant work involving the design of mobile cases and associated packaging. The work included contact with the manufacturer and independent development work.

Summer intern at the Dept. of Engine Analysis and Introductions (NMKD). Work included 3D modeling CAD software. Responsible for assigned cases and participated in daily meetings.

Design Workshop Manager at Linköping University: Responsible for development and maintenance of the prototype workshop.

Charcutier at ICA Supermarket: Sales of perishables over counter in store.

### Education

#### M.Sc. in Product Development

Linköping University Aug 2011 - Jun 2016

#### B.Sc. in Mechanical Engineering

Linköping University Aug 2011 - Jun 2014

#### Military IT Education

Command and Control Regiment, Enköping Jul 2009 - Jun 2010 Advanced courses in product and service development theory and strategy, 3D modeling, eco-design, and project management.

Master thesis within Human Factors Engineering and qualitative user studies.

Studies focused on design and product development with courses within mechanical engineering. Bachelor thesis regarding design for assembly and disassembly of composite components in the automotive industry.

In-depth education in Windows Server 2003, MS SQL 2000, network theory, IT security, usage of classified information and training in troubleshooting and maintenance of networks.

# Other Qualifications

#### Head of Marketing

Dept. of Mechanical Engineering, Linköping University Jan 2015 - Dec 2015

#### Military Data Operations Manager

Command and Control Regiment, Enköping Jul 2009 - Jun 2010 Responsible for the development of graphic profiles, budgets, prints, websites and social networks for SweCAD (CAD fair) and M-YRAN (Dept. of Mechanical Engineering job fair day).

Military service as team leader for four soldiers. The tasks included supervision of the internal information network and maintenance of the network in the field. Demanded leadership skills as well as physical and mental endurance.

## Competences

• • 0 0 0

. . . 0

#### Main Skills

Project Management
Product Design
Service Design
Qualitative Studies

### Language

#### Drivers License

Grade B since 2008

#### Software

Microsoft Project, -Office, -Word, -Excel, -Power Point, Team Center, Catia v.5, Creo Parametrics 2.0, Adobe Photoshop, -Illustrator, -InDesign, -Premiere Pro.